SECRET
Kanta, please! Ryo, take this with you.
Ryo, what are you doing?
Kanta, can I give you my hem?
Ryou, after this...
Ryo, Tomo, you can start hemming now.
Ryo, you can start hemming now.
Kanta, I'm almost finished.
Kanta, it's going up.
Ryo, it's coming up fast!
Kanta, the hemming is almost finished.
Kanta, come on, let's go!
Kanta, just one more roll!
Kanta, it's up!
Kanta, it's good, isn't it?
Kanta, let's go.
Kanta, I'll turn it.
Kanta, yay!
Kanta. Nice to meet you.
Kanta, it's raining.
Kanta, hello everyone.
Kanta, when you get together.
Kanta, we'll be broadcasting here, too.
Kanta, we're going to stream live on YouTube.
Kanta, wow!
Kanta, this is the official instagram.
Kanta: 1,180, 1,200, and more and more!
Kanta I think it's about time.
Kanta We're going to start in earnest.
Kanta So, here we are.
Kanta So, this time, what a surprise!
Kanta We're going to be broadcasting on YouTube and Instagram live.
Kanta, we'll be streaming sports.
Tommy, that's rare!
Tommy, and it's raining!
Tommy, it's a beautiful day.
Kanta, it's really a beautiful day.
Kanta. How about you, Mr. Ryout?
Ryout: Well, the weather is really nice.
Ryout, let's have a fun show.
Kanta, nice to meet you.
Kanta, can you hear me?
Ryout, if you can hear me, please leave a comment.
Kanta, what is it?
Ryout, what's up?
Ryout, I remember that.
Ryout...
Ryout, after Pasico Yokohama Park...
Ryout, what happened suddenly?
Ryout, a video appeared, didn't it?
Ryout, what's that?
Kanta, what?
Kanta, I'm sorry, maybe I imagined it.
Tommy, it's not my imagination!
Tommy, everyone's getting excited.
Kanta, there's been a mistake.
Kanta, there's no miscommunication at Pasico Yokohama.
Kanta, get in the air.
Tommy, no, no, no, no, no!
Kanta, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Tommy, please stand up and talk about me.
Tommy, so, Akutchan, last time on November 5th...
Tommy, you caught it, didn't you?
Tommy, what's going on here?
Tommy, no, it's just a little bit...
Tommy, what was that?
Tommy, there's been a mistake.
Kanta, put it in the air.
Tommy, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Kanta, don't put Ryout on.
Tommy, I'm not wearing a Lyoto.
Tommy, you're a hero.
Kanta, that's cool.
Kanta, how are you?
Kanta, it's true.
Kanta, belly match.
Kanta, the whole world is here.
Kanta.
Kanta, taja hao ao
Kanta, Jiwan Gashia
Tommy, March is coming to an end.
Tommy, we celebrated during the 24th.
Kanta Thank you very much.
Kanta... I'll do this for now.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Now then, the Innista Live show.
This way.
Sudden announcement!
Sorry for the suddennessSorry for the suddenness.
Please look behind you.
I'd like you all to look behind you.
You can see it under my umbrella.
My umbrella
So...
We are here in front of the Pier Arena MM2
and that's why
I'd like to make an announcement.
Can you all hear me?
I would like to make an announcement.
November 5th.
We are the cause of our own problems
In the peer arena MM2
We are going to have our first
Arena One-Man Live at Pier Arena MM2
Let's do it!
It's going to be great.
Thank you very much.
So, I'd like to reiterate
On November 5th at the Pier Arena MM2
We are going to have our first one-man live concert in the arena!
So I'm finally able to announce it!
It's the very last video from Pachinko Yokohama Park.
It's the last video from Pachinko Yokohama Park.
The one that Jun said was poorly distributed.
That video...
It was Pialina's one-man show.
Is everyone here?
Please come in.
Is it on?
This way, please.
So, everyone, a little bit.
We decided on this a long time ago.
About a year ago?
How was it?
How did you feel when you heard about the arena?
I was surprised.
I was surprised, wasn't I?
You were surprised a lot, weren't you?
Yes, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course, of course.
I myself...
I'm a little anxious about it.
Without a doubt.
Our goal for this year 2023 is...
We are here
With all the observers
To have fun together
We at Gaymersloo
That's the goal of the seven of us here at Gaymers Roo.
I hope you will all come and visit us.
I'll tell you the title.
The title is...
Gain is in me arena live 2023
Reversal of the law of cause and effect
Yes, sir.
It's a reversal.
This one is "Gain is in me".
The gain is in me.
It's a message to all of you.
I put it in the title.
I hope you will look into the meaning of the title.
I hope you will look into the meaning
I hope you will think about it.
And more information about tickets and so on...
I'm sure you'll be able to find more information about tickets
I think it will be posted on the official SNS as soon as possible.
Please check it out!
Yes, what do you think of Kazuto-san?
Isn't he too big?
I'm looking forward to it!
You can see how big he is when you get close to him.
Also, we don't feel like it's real yet, but I think it's going to become more and more real.
But I'm sure it's going to become more and more real.
I'm sure the rehearsal people will do their best
I think we will show the culmination of our efforts.
Please come, everyone!
Please come!
We'll be waiting for you.
Also
I started Insta.
I've started Insta.
Please follow me!
So, everyone.
Please look forward to the future gain I have in store for you too!
Today's Insta-live
and YouTube streaming as well.
Thank you very much for both of them.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Please give my best regards again to yourself.
Bye-bye.
See you later.
Okay? See you later.
That's everybody.
Bye-bye.
Okay, bye.
One shot.
Yes, sir.
Three twenty-one.
Yes.
Hello?
Yes!
As an official unit
We will be activated
This video is available
YouTube.
It's publicly available
Thank you for watching.
See you soon
Next time
See you again
See you soon!
Bye-bye.